

# MILOŠ PETROVI Ć (21)

## FRONT END DEVELOPER

## ABOUT

Web developer with 4+ years of experience in structuring, developing and implementing interactive websites. Innovative use of technology and SEO to drive traffic and engage users. Able to complete projects efficiently and satisfy customers with attractive, user-friendly and responsive websites.

#### LANGUAGES

Serbian (Native)

English (Fluent)

Germany (B1)

## SKILLS

HTML/CSS

Bootstrap / Tailwind

VueJS / ReactJS

NativeScript / JavaScript

Laravel (PHP) / SQL

WordPress / OctoberCMS

Search Engine Optimization

Photoshop / Illustrator

#### CONTACT

Belgrade, Serbia +381 69 505 909 9 milosptr@hotmail.com

#### **EDUCATION**

2012-2016 • Grammar school in Zaječar

Information technologies

2016-pres Faculty of Mathematics - University of Belgrade

Information technologies and computer science

### EXPERIENCE

2014-2015 • Graphic designer & PR member

Union of secondary School students of Serbia

(NGO)

2015-pres • CEO & Web developer & Designer

AS Media - Marketing Agency

2015-2016 • WordPress developer & Marketing member

Union of secondary School students of Serbia

(NGO)

2017-2017 • WordPress developer / designer

jan-mar Gafner Media - Switzerland

2017-2018 Front End Developer & Team Leader

eTech 360 (United States)

2018-2019 • Front End Developer

Jungo digital solutions

2018-2019 Co-founder & React / AngularJS Developer

https://www.najletovi.rs/

2019-pres Full Stack Developer & App Developer

Morph Networks